Guide to the Nelson J. Shaulis papers, 1941-1986.
Shaulis, Nelson J. papers, 1941-1986
- Slides - 1975 tour, 1975 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Concord growth, 1958 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. pot lot, 1959 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. roots, Biotron, 1960 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Biotron, 1961 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Biotron, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Geneva pot lot, 1965-1968 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vineyard lab, Fredonia, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Treated shoots and vines, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Glyphosate application to open land, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Monsanto bind. control, Dudley, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Monsanto, non-convolvulus, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Monsanto Concord and C. arvensis, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Monsanto Concord tolerance, mat. Vines, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Monsanto C.sepium control, M. David, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Monsanto Concord tolerance, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dichlobenil, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Karmex, Princip., see regarding bindweed, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Dudley bindweed, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Weed control - chemicals, tillage, temperature effect, 1957-1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - 2,4-D wax bar, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - 2,3-6 responses Trysben, 1957-1959 (Box 34)
- Slides - 2,4-D assay include 1964 field redistribution, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - G.A., dry, 1958 (Box 34)
- Slides - Alar, dry, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Ethrel, dry, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Mechanized harvest, 1960-1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Training for mechanized harvest, 1958-1964 (Box 34)
- Slides - Harvester, 1964-1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Mechanized harvest and shielding, 1965-1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Lewis harvester, 1968 (Box 34)
- Slides - Harvester 3, 1965-1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Phylloxeratin, 1953-1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vineyard 1 photosythesis trial, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Pot size, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Geneva pot lot, shoot no. and Alar, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Pot lot and shade experiment, 1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Biotron, find key, 1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Pot lot shade and sun, 1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Biotron, 1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Biotron, 1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Biotron, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. pot lot, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. pot lot, 1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Grape harvest, 1959-1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Non-dup. not prime material, canopies and harvest yields, 1959-1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vine vigor, West Tier, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Double trunks, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Trellis, 1962-1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - 4.5 x 4.5, 5 x 10 spacing equipment, 1961-1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Concord canopy, 1969-1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Keuka sites, weather study, 1961-1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Cold injury, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Delaware bloom and cold injury, 1962-1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Loomis site, 1965 (Box 34)
- Slides - Analysis of vineyard performance factors (Box 34)
- Slides - GDC equipment including Michigan sprayer, 1966-1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - GDC good, 1966-1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - GDC support arms, 1964-1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Potassium deficiency, 1952-1973 (Box 34)
  Includes 2 empty slide frames with notes
- Slides - Mechanized harvesting (Box 34)
- Slides - Unlabeled, yields and vineyard, ca. 1954 (Box 34)
- Slides - Hurricane Agnes at Widmer, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Replant, 1956, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Polarity, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Training, non-div., 1961-1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Training div. GDC and GTC, 1965-1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Canopy and charts, P. May, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Spacing, 1944-1949 (Box 34)
- Slides - Shoots, ret. Node, 1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vertical cordon (Box 34)
- Slides - Taylor Delaware replant, 1968 (Box 34)
- Slides - Concord, Geneva, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Unlabeled chart II3, SS (Box 34)
- Slides - Hail injury, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Grape roots, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vineland, Ontario, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - To file, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
  Includes Michigan sprayer, rotary vacuum belt, unknown grape malady, Concord leaf
- Slides - Dup. sets of acid SS paper, ca. 1962-1972 (Box 34)
  Fredonia grape studies
- Slides - Dup. S.10878, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Shoot-load experiment, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. weed control, 1966-1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. shoot direction, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. wine trail, Fredonia, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vineland, Ontario, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Weed control data, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Karmex, dry, Yg vine, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Ammate, 1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Weed control, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Yg vine, Karmex, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Princep, Fredonia, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Karmex, 1956 (Box 34)
- Slides - Interrelationship of practices (Box 34)
- Slides - Hail experiment, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Loomis, May 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Site Selection, 1947-1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vines indexing, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - People - Daly, Barton, Shepardson, 1954-1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Chateau Gay, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Polyethylene, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Geography and yields (Box 34)
- Slides - Carbon Dioxide fixation, Vineland, Ontario, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Grape nursery, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Deep placement of potassium, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Concord cane morphology, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Bright Wine Co. sign, 1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Cimagi experiment (Box 34)
- Slides - 2x2s of European, 1961 (Box 34)
- Slides - Cane maturity, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Shoot positioning and directions (Box 34)
- Slides - Yield, SS, Tong (Box 34)
- Slides - Stat (Box 34)
- Slides - Growth habits of varieties, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Cold injury, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Taylor 5279 bud break, 1968 (Box 34)
- Slides - Herb. glyphosate, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Herb. ammate, 1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - 2,4-D, ca. 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Weeds, 1962-1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dudley bindweed casavon, 1954-1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Magnesium, 1954 (Box 34)
- Slides - Potassium deficiency, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Oxidant stipple, non-Concords, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, Fredonia training best slides, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, grafts, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, sprouts, bud break, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, bloom, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, iron chlorosis, 1973 (Box 34)
  Divider, but slide #68 missing
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, Geneva - shoots, cold injury, etc., 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, Muscadines, etc., 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, mineral deficiency, etc., 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, mechanical cluster thinning, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, mineral deficieny, injuries, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, young vines, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, canopies, etc., 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, weed control, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, GA cluster thinning, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, light and shoot development, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1, clusters, CVS, field pictures, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, clusters and leaves, CVS, studio pictures, etc., 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, Concord, glyphosate, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, nodes, ripening, glyphosate, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, wood quality, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, bud development, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, fruitfulness of shoots, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, base buds, 1974 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, muscadine buds, 1974 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, base buds continued, 1974 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, Aurore leaf senescence, 1974 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 1B, incomplete or no label, 1973-1980 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 2, cold injury, Howell, 1976 (Box 34)
  Includes note that suggests slides 309-313 and 318-321 are elswhere in a plastic holder for book plate
- Slides - Viticulture book 2, berry, lenticels, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Viticulture book 2, 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides- Germany (Box 34)
- Slides- Austria (Box 34)
- Slides- Hungary (Box 34)
- Slides- Davis, California (Box 34)
- Slides- Italy (Box 34)
- Slides- Miscellaneous (Box 34)
- Slides- France (Box 34)
- Slides- Leaf Work, 1961 (Box 34)
- Slides- Vineyards, 1961 (Box 34)
- Slides- Virus (Box 34)
- Slides-Colman (Box 34)
- Slides-London (Box 34)
- Slides- Burgundy (Box 34)
- Slides- Champagne (Box 34)
- Slides- Bordeaux (Box 34)
- Slides-Hamton and Windsor (Box 34)
- Slides- Freiburg (Box 34)
- Slides- Lausanne (Box 34)
- Slides- Rhine (Box 34)
- Slides- Vineyards, Viticulture, 1951-1986 (Box 35)